PUTU ANGGI SURYANTARI

 $+6282194802162 \mid putuanggi 03@gmail.com\\ Surabaya, Indonesia$

I am a hard worker both in the team and individually. My dedication to work is high, especially in providing the best quality in everything I do. I am adaptable in terms of new environments and communication between colleagues, new things are something that I like. To apply work ethics, I really value time and look neat at work. I possess skills as a junior UI/UX Designer, specializing in creating engaging interfaces through Figma. My expertise lies in translating ideas into refined design prototypes. I am proactive in resolving issues, utilizing my analytical mindset and innovative approach to tackle intricate design problems and enhance user experiences.

EDUCATION

Universitas Pembangunan Nasional "Veteran" Jawa Timur

August 2021 - Present

Bachelor of Information Systems (GPA of 3.72 / 4.00)

EXPERIENCE

Volunteer Admin May 17, 2023 - Present

Instagram UPA PKK UPN "Veteran" Jawa Timur

- Maintain interaction with followers.
- Design content to go live and Schedule content to go live.
- · Maintain Password Confidentiality and Account Security.

Interns January 17 - June 25, 2023

Editor International Journal (IJEEIT) Narotama

• Review, coordinate the review process, and edit submitted articles to ensure quality, suitability, and conformity with the journal's standards.

Master of Ceremony June 23-24, 2023

Rapat Kerja Nasional & BIMTEK FIK UPNVJT

· Become a link between the event and the audience, and ensure the smooth and entertainment of the event.

Secretary January 2, 2023 - Present

Unit Kesatuan Kerohanian Hindu 2023

· Responsible for organizing and managing committee documents, both physically and digitally.

Responsible for organizing and mana

Master of Ceremony

February 23, 2023

UPA Pengembangan Karir & Kewirausahaan UPNVJT

· Become a link between the event and the audience, and ensure the smooth and entertainment of the event.

Secretary and Steering Commite

February 20 - May 28, 2023

Dharmasanti 2023

• Bridging communication between the UPN Dharmasanti Committee and the Banjar Rungkut Committee. As well as being responsible for organizing and managing committee documents, both physically and digitally.

Secretary and Treasurer

August 16 – October 26, 2022

October 5 - November 28, 2021

Welcome Party 2022

• Responsible for organizing and managing committee documents, both physically and digitally. As well as managing the committee budget.

Chief Executive November 11 - December 11, 2022

SUKSESI 2023

• Plan, organize, supervise, communicate, solve problems, and evaluate events or projects for which he is responsible.

Secretary August 2 - December 30, 2022

Unit Kesatuan Kerohanian Hindu 2022

Responsible for organizing and managing committee documents, both physically and digitally.

Commite October 19 – 21, 2022

The 2022 IEEE 8th International Seminar (ITIS)

• Coordinate events, ensure the availability of necessary technical facilities, accompany reviewers.

Senior Companion September 3 - October 7, 2022

Action of Scientific Papers 2022

• Sharing relevant experience and knowledge, assisting in important decision making, supervising and directing participants' activities.

Master of Ceremony October 9, 2022

Welcome Party 2022

· Become a link between the event and the audience, and ensure the smooth and entertainment of the event.

Member of Public Relations Division

Welcome Party 2021

 Manage communication and relationships between the committee and campus, promote events or projects to the public, manage social media and digital content, establish partnerships with external parties, and disseminate information and organize media attendance at events.

PROJECT

Website Raka Cipta Mahajana

June, 2023

Website Programming Course Project

- · Website development using Bootstrap, PHP, and JavaScript programming languages
- · Edit the appearance of the website with Bootstrap to make it look attractive and responsive
- Successfully completed this website within 3 weeks

Web-based data warehouse dashboard

June, 2023

Data Warehouse Course Project

- Website development using HTML, CSS, PHP, Bootstrap, and JavaScript programming languages CodeIgniter as the framework
- · Work with two partner to accomplish this website
- · Successfully completed this website within 3 weeks

UI/UX Design of Student Printing Information System Gui at Photocopy Partners

Desember, 2022

E-Business course project

- Responsible for creating UI/UX design using figma
- · Work with 2 other team members to create a final project report
- Successfully completed the task on time and got an A

UI/UX Design of Student Complaint Information System at W.R. Supratman University

Desember, 2022

Information System Design Analysis course project

- · Responsible for creating UI/UX design using figma
- · Work with 2 other team members to create a final project report
- · Successfully complete tasks on time

ACHIEVEMENT

- . 1st National Singing Contest Event Online Champions Vol III
- 4th Finalis Karya Tulis Ilmiah (Group) Universitas Hang Tuah
- 2nd National Singing Contest Kencana Event Bali
- 3rd National Singing Contest Event Online Champions Vol I
- 3rd National Singing Contest Univesitas Nahdlatul Ulama

SOFT SKILL

- · Teamwork
- Communication
- · Study Hard Time
- · Management
- · Critical Thinking
- Leadership
- · Creativeness
- · High initiative

HARD SKILL

- Microsoft Word
- · Microsoft Excel
- · Microsoft Power Point
- Canva
- Figma
- · Visual Studio Code
- · Organization Mangement
- · Digital Marketing
- Literacy
- Photography
- · Design

LANGUAGE

- Indonesia
- Inggris (Intermedite)